

# **Full Stack Developer**

Phone: (520) 709-1298

Email: art a henry@yahoo.com Website: https://arthur-portfolio

Linkedin: linkedin.com/arthur-henry-contact info

Address: 43469 West Caven Drive Maricopa, AZ. 85138

#### Summarv

As a software developer my responsibilities vary from day-to-day, allowing for a wide variety of experiences and challenges from project-to-project. I'm able to provide best business practice for design, development and execution of software solutions.

### Core Competencies

JavaScript Linux HTML5 CSS3 Bash Rest API Angular React MongoDB Maven NodeJS **MySOL** 

### Professional Experience

ELPHA, San Francisco,

August 2021 – Present

## CA. Full Stack Developer

- Develop automated work-flows using Linux Bash scripting alongside NodeJS, Spring Boot, MySQL.
- Build scalable back-end systems using NodeJS, complemented by JavaScript for front-end experiences.
- Expertise in database management using MySQL, crafting efficient queries to support robust application functionalities. Seamlessly integrate Bash scripts with NodeJS and Spring Boot applications for streamlined Dev Ops practices.
- Proficient in JavaScript, employing modern frameworks to create interactive user interfaces while leveraging MySQL for back-end data storage and retrieval.

HEWLETT PACKARD, Phoenix, AZ.

June 2017 – August 2021

### Front End Developer

- Develop a customer support platform, using Angular.
- Understanding Angular component logic, and developing a layout of an application.
- Create SPA's for login for main page containing favorites and page for continuous integration configuration.
- Build and execute a brand new customer resolution management tool using Angular and Java to efficiently monitor, encode, and resolve customer questions and concerns.
- Work with payment team to save over 50,000 customers time and improve cash flow through development of modern, responsive customer experience.

SPRINT-PARANET, Chicago, IL.

*March* 2013 – *June* 2017

## Senior Software Engineer

- Work with engineering managers to develop and improve world-class coding standards, design
- Build applications with reliability and scalability to meet customer demands.
- Develop, document, test, and debug new and existing software systems and applications.
- Modify HTML, JavaScript, and CSS web pages to optimize the page's performance for faster loading and browsing.
- Worked in a team environment to develop and maintain business solutions to increase profits through adopting an Agile approach.

#### Education

**Keller Graduate School of Management** Master Degree

Master's in Computer Information Systems June 2016 to August 2018

**DeVry University Bachelor** Degree

Bachelor's in Computer Science March 2011 to June 2015